do you think men can give birth I think
that uh yes or no question I think that
a person who is assigned male at Birth I
don't think they a signed male at Birth
so people are not male at Birth I think
that a person see your evidence that
college is a scam my friend so what do
you say in some cases women without your
these are murderers of course not
they're not murderers we the difference
between an IUD killing a conceived
zygote and like a mother going to
Planned Parenthood and killing the petus
in her room that was actually the best
point somebody made it's not about the
the cells it's not about no no no I'm
speaking no I'm speaking no I'm speaking
no I'm speaking no I'm speaking no I'm
speaking no I'm speaking hello everyone
I am Charlie Kirk founder of Turning
Point USA and uh I am surrounded by 20
woke college
kids my first prompt is abortion is
murder and should be
[Music]
illegal all right can I maybe go
okay hello what's your name Juliana nice
to meet you nice to meet you can we get
our terms right first yeah okay abortion
is the forcible ending of the viability
of a being in utero otherwise known as a
fetus do we agree that's what abortion
is okay yeah okay great and then murder
is the intentional taking of Life
different than killing or sudden death
so murder would be the intent with
intent taking another life do we agree
with that okay okay and then we agree
that murder in general in society should
be illegal yeah okay great so yeah no I
do want to preface that I'm a Catholic
so I think one really important thing
that the Bible says is to not judge and
just going back to the topic um I think
there's a big difference uh between you
know cells in utero than a living
breathing existing being and while um I
do believe it's murder and that's just
my personal belief right I don't believe
in telling people what to do with their
bodies that's not up to me and it's not
up to us as well as Christians to judge
should we prevent murder in society for
sure yeah I should be illegal but I
think that it's really different right
because you know these people
aren't sorry nice to meet you okay nice
to
[Music]
meet okay what's your name NAA nice to
meet you okay can I just ask um at how
many weeks do you think that a fetus is
V viable well viability and moral worth
are two different things no but I'm
asking you at how many weeks do you 20
weeks a baby can survive outside of
utero so it's actually 24 to 26 weeks 20
the youngest ever in a niku unit
actually happened in San Diego not far
from here and Sur survived at 20 weeks
okay so under roie Wade 93% of abortions
happened in the first 13 weeks of
pregnancy that's 93% of the abortions
happened well before a fetus is
technically viable as a form of let's go
into VI ability so what is it about
let's say a six week baby that has a
heartbeat its own DNA fingerprint brain
waves that is less moral worth than an
88-year-old right now with dementia in a
home down the street that person
requires assistance requires help what
why is it that the six week baby is of
less moral worth well first of all it's
not a baby it's a fetus what does fetus
mean a fetus is in utero what does fetus
mean in Latin what the I'm sorry is this
a it means little human being
his smile is very creepy okay um smiling
is creepy no your smile specifically but
let's go back to we're losing track here
no but but is what species is the fetus
the fetus is not a species yet it's
technically classified as a parasite
until it is viable now I want to talk I
can't really get past that are you
saying you saying a baby is a disease or
a tumor a parasite is not a disease and
a tumor those are not the same thing a
parasite is defined as something that
cannot survive outside its host a baby
before it is viable cannot survive
outside of a woman's womb got it so
let's let's extrapolate that is not a
living organism are are old people with
Alzheimer's and Dementia that are being
assisted every day are they parasites no
they're not parasites they're human
beings who are on the brink of death got
it so my going my four-month-old that
requires mom's breast milk and requires
daily changes and feedings cannot
survive without its own is my
four-month-old the parasite your baby
can breathe on its own your baby can
drink water from its mouth to its
stomach but but it canot your bab can
eat can it hunt can it gather can it
reason but that's not what qualifies
something as being a living organism
being a living organism simply means can
you survive outside of a womb outside of
your host got it so I just want to make
sure I'm clear why does that then equate
to moral viability it equates to
Scientific viability why under what
standard because it is not alive and you
are advocating for the rights of
something that is not technically a life
got it so what is is something while
sacrificing the needs of the human woman
who is alive got it so but a a a mom can
survive yes without the baby in her uhuh
right yes the baby cannot survive
without the mom yes but a mom cannot
survive without her lungs so it's not
her body it's in her body it's not her
DNA so it's not her choice so it's a it
actually is directly her DNA it's it is
100% it's 50% of her DNA after
DNA he's going to win I'm telling you
this this this this could take a while
okay first of all do we have our terms
correct we agree actually no so first of
all I'd like to refine our terms I have
two points to bring up after that though
so you Define murder is like
intentionally like killing a human being
I think that's a very poor way to Define
murder because if someone were to like
break into my home and point a gun at
the heads of me and everybody I love and
I intentionally kill them to prevent
them from un from killing my family I
don't think I murdered them right so I
would Define murder as the unjustified
termination of a human life you're
making a good point let me further
clarify then so self-defense is very
warranted exactly right but I I can see
where you're going to go with how that
has to go with abortion but we can go
down that journey in a second yeah so I
mean like I I kind of do want to give
you my argument and so far as why I'm
pro-choice why I think it's Justified
but first I think that you know your
position is quite absurd right because
you're saying that it is murder to kill
a human being right at any point in
development especially when it's in the
mother's wom my question to you would be
well does this make women with iuds
murderers because it is the case that in
some scenarios an IUD will allow for
conception to occur meaning there's a
unique human life there but it will
prevent its implantation intentionally
killing it well no preventing
implantation is not necessarily the same
thing as terminating a fertilized egg
for example if you take Plan B for again
it's not it's not the same thing
preventing the production of proest
progesterone is not the same thing as
terminating a fully a a being that has
been fertilized you do not know for a
fact that the egg has been fertilized
you do not know that when even IUD okay
yeah so preventing a fertilization or
implantation to the uter lining is
killing a conceived zygote so what
happens a sperm goes into the egg right
the egg becomes fertilized it's a
conceived zygote in some cases it will
prevent the implantation of the
conceived zygote killing the conceived
zygote in some cases correct so what do
you say in some cases women are
murderers of course not they're not
murders we do not know for a case that's
that's like saying that every so what's
the difference between an IUD killing a
conceived zygo like a mother going to
plann Parenthood and killing the fetus
in her room well so you asking you're
asking two separate things if they if
they knew for certain to be more clear
that I have a fertilized egg and I'm
going to take a drug to prevent that
fertilized egg from attaching to their
uterin wall then yes that is an act of
killing or murder of course okay so do
you think all murderers should go to
jail do I think all murderers should go
to jail I mean on the third on third
degree murder however no I don't think
women that got abortions or had iuds
should go to jail because I think that
they have been deceived by mass culture
M Mass propaganda secondly the people
who should go to jail are the
abortionists who are the ones that have
been putting the abortion pill the ones
that have been doing procedures the ones
that have been going into the third
trimester and breaking babies backs and
inserting them with syringes while the
babies are crying and suffocating being
born alive and then being dead on the
operating table that is who should go to
jail
oh that was actually the best point
somebody made we'll have to we'll have
to talk about
[Music]
it okay whenever I'm talking about this
discussion
um I always go to the question of what
about in The Case of the mother when her
life is in danger because I'm a big
believer I don't I don't know I'm still
iffy on if I think it's a or if it's
murder or not but even so I mean I don't
want to say murder is Justified guys
wait let me just get this one point and
then you can vote me out give me one
second um say the mother gets pregnant
and she knows that if she gives birth
she's going to die she has some kind of
Health complication then what do you do
in section I don't know what that means
to C-section they an ins guys wait hold
on give me one second go right they go
right below the belly button and they
deliver the baby and therefore she
doesn't have to give birth it's
technically birth but it's much safer so
that's that's actually safer than an
abortion
procedure sorry sorry
[Music]
Lily hello how are you hi what's your
name Deen nice to meet nice to meet you
um I would say with abortion I think uh
it's it's very complicated but I think
the issue that I have primarily with
your stance of being pro-life that
there's no Nuance um there's women who
are being forced to travel hundreds of
miles to access abortion care even in
cases of rape in certain States that're
they're not giving any sort of um
allowance for that and I think um you
know a lot of people who are pro-life
they they say that they're pro-life but
I feel like they're really Pro birth
because in you know with Firearms uh the
United States has some of the highest
firearm deaths um out of oecd Nations
right and we can acknowledge that that's
for children who are actually living in
um so I feel like abortion while yeah it
is I can I can definitely see your point
I I just think that it should be allowed
in some circum yeah great um I'm happy
to get into the gun violence stuff later
but I want to really stay focused on
abortion right you can see you can say
you see my point can you see the world
also where since we know it's a human
life that it should be illegal since we
don't allow murder in our society well
that's that's that's where I have an
issue because abortion is not being done
willy-nilly it's it's like the life of
the mother's always how many abortions
do you think we have every day in
America guess I'm not sure I'm not sure
guess I I'm I'm honestly not sure maybe
I don't know a th000 4,000 a day so it
is kind of willy-nilly we have
1.6
[Music]
sorry hello hi um I just want to clarify
the thing that you're aiming for is less
abortion right that would be you would
want or at least eventually it's also a
protection of those that can't protect
themselves but yes and that's why once
we after the reversal of Row versus Wade
we saw abortions go down dramatically in
Texas Alabama Mississippi we saw
thousands of babies that are now alive
and well that are able to have amazing
lives thanks to the reversal of Row
versus weight uh I don't think a lot of
that is true um it is but it's not true
because when you make abortion illegal
it doesn't actually decrease the amount
of ab a nice talking point in Texas the
numbers show differently birth has gone
up yeah legal goes down but illegal
abortions still happen abortions still
happen outside of whatever data you're
show that's not true but let's just say
so 40% so well if you if you want to
well first of all if you count the
abortion pill you're right but that's a
separate thing than a chemic chemical
abortion and surgical abortion different
things and I'm not debating I'm not I'm
not debating you I'm debating her so if
you want to do the flags and come back
in try and be faster next time so let me
ask you this so the question is we
should try to limit unjust suffering of
human beings right sure okay that's my
position is that there's unjust
suffering of anywhere between 1.4 to 1.6
million abortions a year of human beings
that are being massacred in the womb and
so that's not a woman's rights issue
that's not a men's rights issue that's
just a human rights issue okay the best
way to decrease abortions happening is
proper sex education limiting abortion
and making abortion illegal does not
actually decrease the amount of
abortions that happen so what is your
evidence of that what is my evidence of
that because we have increased sex
education last 30 years we've had no our
sex education is so bad in America well
by bad what do you mean by that we have
we have more access to birth control for
young kids we have more kids that are
learning you birth control at a younger
age we have more of that in our public
school system and we've seen all the
trends actually go in a negative
Direction so in fact we see that the
more sex exucation there is the the more
disturbing those Trends are so you say
that let me ask just one more thing you
say that if we make abortion illegal
people will still do it should we then
just make gang violence legal because no
I'm saying if you actually wanted to
decrease the amount of abortions that
happen you wouldn't be advocating for a
like to make abortion illegal you'd be
advocating for Alles that logic apply to
stealing looting kidnapping ARS sin and
murder well actually it does because
those are results of different societal
issues that you should be educating
yourself on rather than making ital
front can we should we make kidnapping
arson burgly murder legal because
they're symptoms of something else we
should be helping Society heal from
those things got answer the question we
want less of those things so we just
make them legal will get less
looting you know actually I'm going to
let someone else thank you very much
[Music]
hi Parker nice to meet you yes nice to
meet you Charlie big Tick Tock guy here
so like uh pedophiles people who were
married to children in the past and
normalized in that Society should they
go to prison should pedophiles like if
you could go back in time would you put
those pedophiles in prison that was that
married those children because it was
normalized they were deceived into
thinking it's okay would you put them in
prison you had to slow down file should
get the death penalty no so you'd go
back in the past you give them the death
penalty even though they were deceived
into thinking it was okay but you said
people who get abortions who are women
shouldn't go to pris but it's not
currently illegal okay regardless at
that time at that time it wasn't no I
would not go back and retroactively
enforce laws where things were currently
not illegal you wouldn't put pedophiles
in prison in the past hold on a second
when was it ille when was it legal in
America well child marriage was legal in
America throughout the early 1900s and
especially throughout most of society
for thousands of years especially in the
Old Testament and in the Bible hold well
hold on hold on a second so where where
where is the levitical law that allows
you to marry a child oh yeah can you
name the verse so well I can't name the
first but the particular conditions that
are enlisted in the Bible are that you
have to beat physical maturity and
emotional maturity which is extremely
vague and throughout Society has been
seen there is not a verse but let's kind
of go back back under your VI let's go
back to well generally agreed upon it's
18 years old but let me ask you but you
but you because you you don't go based
on what's General you go based on the b
i I say 18 years old but let me ask you
a question where's when when does Life
Begin conception like conception great
so good so should we protect our life at
conception I care about Senti in life
not not so when do brain waves start you
think brain dead people should be able
to pull the plug on like family should
be able to pull the plug on individual
got to answer the question when do brain
when do brain waves when do brain waves
start uh you can see brain waves around
6 to 8 weeks which in brain dead
individual there are brain waves as well
so the brain waves necessary to produce
a subjective experience are met until
around 2 can you see it from my
perspective that at six to eight weeks
those brain waves will actually increase
not decrease if allowed the process of
development to continue did you know
those same EEG scans exist in brain dead
people that you don't think are the
difference with the brain dead people is
that the likelihood of those brain waves
actually increasing is very low at 6 to
eight weeks when by 15 weeks they can
hear the it's irreversible sensation
that's what brain death is I know that
it's not coma but you're you're you're
doing a red herring go back to it's not
what's a red herring six a red herring
is where you you avoid the topic and you
say something that is uh adjacent or
symmetrical to what I'm saying but not
actually I'm saying me that's not that's
not a red herring a six to8 week baby if
they're allowed to continue to develop
what ends up happening uh at a certain
point it will become a sentient being in
the future the same way if I keep
engaging with my girlfriend there'll be
a baby in the future yet I don't care
about unless you're infertile which we
don't know but so let's let's see let's
see the the process of development right
why answer my question why do you have
the ability or the right should those
child P3 go to prison the process of
should the pedophiles Go to Prison from
1904 how many pedophiles are alive from
1904 they're not alive right I meant
like if you can go back in the past
hypothetically speaking and you could
put them in prison would you put them in
prison I would have killed them myself
if I was aive back okay so then so then
you don't apply it based upon what
people are deceived to believe you apply
based on what you consider
think should
whys CL constructive debate if you keep
on talking over me I was finishing my
statement you were talking over me let
me ask you a very simple question do you
think it would be a good thing if we had
less abortions in America um it depends
on the context like are the abortions
prior to sentience yes all abortions
yeah no it would not be necessarily
better unless it is the case of the
people didn't want the abortions and it
would be negatively impactful to their
health medically speaking L abortion uh
after sentience yes okay so you you
believe in an 8we abortion ban yeah no
no no I don't I don't sorry I believe in
an abortion ban after 18 through 26
weeks okay that's that's a more
reasonable position I have to give you
credit for that it's similar to Trump's
15 weeks yeah so why why do you think
that most people don't share your view
on that um well people just don't know
really know what sentience is there's
not a lot of conversation about abortion
and these conversations are very
difficult like they're conceptually hard
to go through and I understand why a lot
of people don't understand their
positions on it I think people cutting
off I thought thought we weren people I
was actually complimenting
[Music]
I how are you nice to see you um so I
just have one question there's like in
any case you don't think there's any
case where abortion should be legal
there's a very very rare couple cases
okay so you do think that a couple cases
it is legal if if if cesarian section is
not going to save the mother's life and
the mother's life is actually at risk
which is debated amongst growing numbers
of OBGYNs okay that is the only case
where abortion should be should be
allowed but people say it is a growing
consensus in the pro-life world that
abortion is never medically necessary
okay so if you had a daughter and she
was 10 and she got raped and she was
going to give birth and she no wait oh
and she was going to give birth and she
was going to live would you want her to
go through that and carry her that's
that's awfully graphic answer it's no
but it's a real life scenario that
happens to many people the answer is yes
the baby would be delivered okay great
so I that's insane um but let me tell
you why no hold on let me ask you a
question there's two ultrasounds I have
one is a baby conceived in one is a baby
conceived by a loving couple which one
is which which which person
here which person here was conceived by
tell me which one was conceived by you
don't know exactly cuz it's all human
rights and it's all human beings matter
it's but it's about your daughter who's
passed to give birth to it and it's
going to be tortured by that for the
rest of her life that's going to take
away every freedom she's ever going to
have that's going to ruin her life she's
going to grow up and going vitim crime
the the point is how you were conceived
is irrelevant to what human rights you
get when hold on one second if a person
conceiv the walks down the side of the
street it's not like they don't get
First Amendment rights or second
amendment rights or the worst thing to
do to that do the daughter is to then
say hey we're going to go murder the
being in inside of you they wouldn't
even know like listen they they wouldn't
know listen listen listen listen but
wouldn't it wouldn't a better story to
say something evil happened and we do
something good in the face of evil
instead of saying we're going to do evil
and then murder the being because we're
going to we're going to we're going to
Pander to the evil no what makes what
makes the West great is that we do good
after evil not evil after evil it's not
about the being and the the cells it's
not about no no no I'm speaking no I'm
speaking no I'm speaking I'm speaking no
I'm speaking no I'm speaking no I'm
speaking no I'm speaking no I'm speaking
thank you so it's not I'm not talking
about that I'm talking about the person
no I'm talking about the person who is
dealing with the pregnancy I am not
talking about the cells I don't I don't
care listen the fetus the whatever I
don't care about that right now until it
is
formed there is if there is a 5-year-old
child who is pregnant and the baby is
two weeks in can't get pregnant actually
they have and they have given birthy old
have given pregnant correct there is one
recorded case of a 5-year-old birth is
that is that is that common yes not it's
common for 5-year-old get sometimes and
it's they get pregnant I think they
should be able to have medical access to
something that could save not only just
their life but like their Lively Hood
how many how many I'm curious how many I
hope your daughter lives a very happy
life and gets away from you okay so that
is really nasty and so her her belief
system just so we're clear is that the
time's up yeah no I got it it's fine I
mean it's insanely nasty and we'll talk
again my next claim is that college is a
scam hello hello hello what's your name
I'm Maddox how are you doing good so
college is a scam well let's define our
terms College being traditional for your
college of course University not
Community College or Technical College
course a scam if we can agree on a
definition is where a majority of people
who will go through the institution or
business uh they're not getting their
money's worth their time's worth um and
they're being deceived when they sign up
so do we agree on those terms yeah
perfect okay well what would further
definitions what do you think is the
purpose of going to college the purpose
of college should be a traditional
liberal arts education the pursuit of
what is good true and beautiful okay
that's not what it is uh it should be
the betterment of yourself and your soul
uh nurturing your character uh and
becoming a better citizen understanding
the deeper things in life at the very
least though it should be preparing one
for the job market do you think college
does those things I think it does uh but
I would add on to your point that I
think not only is it for the betterment
of your s but it's the for the
betterment of society we need historians
we need certain majors that may not make
as much money I think those are for the
betterment of society would you agree
that there's some Majors that may not
make money but are still essential to it
depends do you think that getting a
degree in gender studies is good for
society uh I would agree yeah why why
would studying gender not be good for
study well learning that men can give
birth is not exactly a good use of time
is it is that what they're teaching in
college right now colleges yeah
according to the Center for Disease
Control they no longer say women can
give birth they say birthing person
okay do you think men can give birth do
I think men can give birth I think that
uh yes or no question I think that a
person who is assigned male at Birth I
don't think they assign mail at Birth so
people are not male at Birth I think
that a person see you're evidence that
college is a scam my friend college is a
scam you're not you're lacking in a lot
of here we can continue right now so
gender studies do you think that
studying gender is uh uh not Essential
should we not deepen our first of all I
don't think gender we're going to get
there later I don't think gender exists
I think that there are two Sexes
infinite personalities and genders
however let's get back to the core
contention can I ask my question again
real quick well I want to get back to my
core contention a scam so the majority
of kids that go to college if they end
up getting a job at all they end up
getting a job that does not require a
college degree do you think that certain
jobs that may not associate with a
direct major can incorporate skills that
you learn from a major I think I'm
personally I'm an econ major and
depending on what job I do in the future
I can still use the skills earned from
so tell me about Milton fredman tell me
about Milton Freedman he is an economist
from how about Thomas Soul Thomas Soul
lud vanus lud well I will say that first
how
about I'd love to see you answer the
gender studies question we will get
there
later that's that's what psychedelics
are for uh who's
[Music]
next um well I think it's difficult to
think about just one major thinking
about just gender studies like sure like
not everyone should be a gender Studies
major we need doctors we need lawyers we
need everything however why does it
matter if 10 people want to be a gender
Studies major and it matters to them
like not everyone can be a lawyer not
everyone can be a doctor there needs to
be some people and you know what yeah it
sucks that some people do go to college
and get a degree and then they end up
not in a Workforce for that but I don't
think that has to do with like college
was a scam it's more like maybe that
just wasn't the path for them or that
life choice was just too hard to get for
them but some people are able to go to
college and get a degree and use it and
that is super important because imagine
if no doctors went to college they just
like I think I can do it well of course
doctors and lawyers need credentialing
right but well less than 5% of all
people that go to college end up
studying medicine or in legal the vast
majority go into soft social sciences
Communications with the humanities so
you're in college or have been is that
correct yeah are you forced to take
classes that you think are a waste of
time yeah I'm for you know what on so
they're taking your money and they're
forcing you that they're a waste of time
that's kind of scammy right oh I think
that some classes o some so you have to
probably go in debt right depends okay
are you going you going are you going
into debt no okay well that's good I
picked a school that actually offered me
a scholarship someone else is paying for
your college oh I I don't know depends
on me I mean that school that wanted to
give me an opportunity but that's not
what we're talking about we're talking
about talking about the scam element
right so you said that there are some
classes that if students had to go into
debt or had to pay for would not be a
good use of their time so it's not
representing students well well do you
think like high school is scam then cuz
I had to pay for high school but I
didn't I'm not going to use AP US
History in my psychology degree ever
well I think AP US History is actually a
really good use of time knowing about
your country and your history and well
but I'm not going to use that in my
career that's what we're talking about
in the career path for college let's go
back to what I said right we said
traditional college right fouryear
college and what a scam is we're a
majority a majority of the people that
will go through the Enterprise the
business or the institution are not
getting their time Worth or their money
worth so therefore I go back to my core
contention which is a majority of kids
that exit College will not use their
degree at all when they go to find a job
but if you ask them do you think college
was a scam I don't think majority of
them are going to say yes some of them
will some of them are going to well not
everyone who's being scammed actively
knows they're being scammed people still
buy erectile dysfunction drugs off the
internet and they get scammed that's
their own personal choice of course
people have choices to be scammed I'm
not saying they don't have a choice I'm
making an observation analysis of the
institution for example flying Spirit
Airlines kind of a scam should be shut
down there is some yeah agree there are
some things in life we have to take a
step back and like oh the consumer is
not being well served you want to shut
down a bunch of majors in colleges that
you think are scams no I never said that
so what would your proposal be to fix
the scam of college there is no proposal
I'm simply the contention is college is
a scam so then what's the point of that
statement to get you to agree but like
what would that do like what do you want
to fix in college that's going to help
in not be a scam let's we can get to
step interval two as long as you can
agree that college is a scam no cuz not
for everyone for me I'm using a degree
that's going to help me help people make
better what are you studying psychology
and criminal justice okay so and it's
being paid for by somebody else which is
which is fine that's good so psychology
and criminal justice um do you do you
absolutely need to get a degree to be
able to get you do yeah I really I mean
like I could I guess study it all on my
own but it's just like makes more sense
to go and have all these experience I'm
getting like wonderful experiences
internships all through my college
that's helping
no it's just that this is a paway that's
really helping me so you know there's 11
million jobs open in the country right
now that don't require a college degree
okay then the people who want those jobs
can go get those jobs I'm not one of
those push too many kids into college no
okay so the national graduation rate is
59% if I asked the room everyone would
agree that they know some people that
went to college that did not graduate
yeah right so we're probably sending too
many kids into this institution but if
they might have been able to do it then
like why is it not worth it to try and
to push yourself to get a better
education and go further that's a bad
thing right but some people are able to
work through that and it's like an
opportunity thing when an institution is
multi-trillion dollars in scale involves
23 million of our citizens every four
years and is not actually better in the
country for example if College was so
great we would see incomes going up for
Gen Z and Millennials we'd see more
people able to own homes kids wouldn't
I'm telling you this is so ableist what
you're doing by the way I'm telling you
right hello what's your name Al nice to
meet you okay so let me start by saying
well first of all you said we're sending
too many kids to college who's sending
them who's forcing them guidance
counselors parents Community are they
forcing them are they signing them up
themselves forcing I never said forcing
but you can have nudging and forcing are
two different things we also subsidize
College through the federal government
so you guys get subsidized interest
rates scholarships and Loans so the
taxpayer is nudging students
and gently and sometimes forcely pushing
them into college and you would agree it
is an expectation if you grow up in a
upper middle class home to go to college
you would agree with that so there's a
societal cultural push I didn't grow up
in an upper middle class so okay well
but do you would you see it from their
would you see how that's that argument
is correct I guess there might be a
pressure but no one's sending them
you're sending yourself well of course
well we're all over the age of 18 right
when you're in college so you're sending
yourself but that's besides let's be
honest I mean for that's a silly
argument
yes they're technically send themselves
I was just at Arizona State University
moving everyone had their parents there
they were co-signing on loans they were
there helping pay for stuff parents the
ones that are still checking in they're
the ones that largely subsidize their
lifestyle hey Mom can you vend me Veno
me 3,000 bucks so that I can go out an
extra night yes of course when you're 18
years old you're the one signing on the
dotted line but there's enormous
pressure and nudging and cultural
expectation that students go to college
right okay I think the problem here is
that it's it's up to the person you're
you're not you can't just go to college
and expect to come out with a degree you
have to put the work in you have to put
the work in you have to make connections
and some people might think college is
just four years of partying and drinking
and making friends whatever but you have
to actually put the work in and if you
put the work in you make connections
then you can find a job right outside of
college well no not not doubting that
you can't find a job it's just that 52%
of them get a job that doesn't require
them to get the degree but most jobs
offer intent to pay if you have a degree
and 86% 86% of people with a degree get
paid more then people with just a high
school diploma that's only if you count
the ones at the top 10% of in income
iners so not if you count Humanities not
if you count um people that study in the
uh social sciences if you count medicine
or you count law that's absolutely
correct however the vast majority of
kids that go to college are not studying
medicine law engineering business
finance they're studying Communications
social scien or Humanities which are on
the lower income ladder so as I
mentioned we have 11 million job
openings in this country right now that
do not require a college degree I'm
guessing in this room that within four
to five years you guys would killed to
be able to earn 80,000 $80 to $100,000 a
year yes do you know that in States
across the country and in cities they're
offering apprenticeships become plumbers
and welders electricians that doesn't
require for your college degree entrance
salary $80,000 a year but again 86% of
people with a bachelor's degree earn
more than people with a high school
dipla no 86% of all people with a
bachelor's degree if you take out the
top 10% it's actually lower than those
that don't go to college so the reason
that number that average goes up is
because the the doctors and the
engineers and the lawyers are the ones
that bring that average so significantly
up but let me ask you a question that do
you think that there's any waste at all
in the current College model do I think
there's any waste I don't think we need
all of it okay good what part um well
you have to start with your core classes
and it's like high school you're taking
the same classes in do you think like
for example um do you think that it's
okay nice to meet you
[Music]
wow I'm Emily nice to meet you Emily
thank you um earlier said that about 5%
of college students are going into
fields of like medicine law and
Engineering was it let let me clarify
yes as far as they're going to be able
to get postgraduate degrees so they will
go all the way up and get their jurist
master or they will end up passing the
bar or becoming a doctor right so it's
easy to say doctors lawyers but Health
Care Professionals if you count nurses
or people that work in healthcare that
number is closer to 20 25% okay so 5% um
who has a doctor can you like raise your
hand if you have a doctor like a medical
doctor a doctor yeah like a medical
doctor yeah you do okay um 5% is still a
lot of people right of course but that
means 95% might not need to exist at the
institution I don't think that's the
takeaway just because 5% which is still
millions of Americans all across board
but if you were to say hey we only have
medical schools only have legal we can
get rid of gender studies get rid of so
what's what's the contention well gender
studies is actually if you look on like
the pre-law track gender studies is a
pre law track if you're going to be a
lawyer you have to study gender studies
and other social cult point that college
is a scam why would why would a lawyer
need to study gender studies should a
lawyer know the law it's a social
science the law you think the law isn't
inadvertently affected by social
cultural and gender Norms of course it
is but shouldn't they first know the
Bill of Rights the Constitution The
Federalist Papers we learned that in
high school okay so what is marber
versus
Madison I haven't been in high school
for a really long time I'm not trying to
be a lawyer Lear yeah so I mean high
schools are brown what was Brown versus
the Board of Education that's for
desegregating school okay good yeah
which project 2025 wants to like defund
the Department of Education who wrote
the Constitution founding fathers 1778 I
don't know it wasn't 17 at 78 I don't
know yeah you don't know no okay well
this is the point is that you don't
learn it in high school you don't even
learn it in undergraduate and our our
law school is not learning it so maybe
well I'm not in law school no the point
is that you were saying they already
learned it and they don't I don't want
this to be a pop quiz or trivia I didn't
go to college and I'm asking you very
basic Civic questions and you're paying
to go to college and you can't answer
them that's so fair but I
think thank you
[Music]
sorry I have a question is church a scam
no because church is honoring the Divine
and the internal and the good and the
true and the Beautiful is college but it
but it deceives people because you you
give a promise of everlasting life which
you don't actually get because
Christianity is contradictory logically
speaking do you want to get into a
theological debate or are we going to
talk about college because I complet
completely disagree Jesus Christ is my
Lord and Savior and we will have eternal
life okay so how if there is a perfect
being that created the world how could
we exist in an imperfect world I'm happy
to have this discussion can we go back
to college though because do you think
because that's a little bit of a red
herring and a little bit of a rabbit
hole tell me what that has to do with
college being a scam well I do think
college can be a scam for certain people
I don't think it's a scam for everyone
for people like me college was very
beneficial for me for sure I'm asking
you based upon your definition of a scam
do you consider the Christian Church a
scam of course not it's giving people
life and treat teaches them goodness
Christianity is false then that's a
deception okay but you think it's false
I don't we can agree to disagree also
I'm not agreeing to disagree on that but
we're not talking about we're not
talking about the church we're talking
about college right so again also people
are not paying to go to church are they
but it's a redu absurdum you know that
is ask the question what's a redu out
ofum uh that's a Latin term that means
reducing down to the lowest common
belief correct yeah so I'm taking am I
right I didn't go to college I knew that
I'm taking your particular position let
let me ask you a question without you
interrupting me do you pay to go to
church uh no I don't some people forced
to pay based upon their particular
denomination in today do you pay to go
to church depending on the church no no
you don't do you have to go to debt and
to go to church uh in some circumstances
people do because they have to give up
10% of their income to be able to do
that which people can't circumstance
well they're LDS you understand that a
lot of LDS Churches specifically require
10% they don't require it and you're
talk do in plenty of places well you're
asking Mainline Christian isn't their
stigmatization if you don't do that okay
you're good at interrupting not good at
answering well you haven't answered any
of my questions yet I did say no church
is not a scam church is the bride of
Christ college is a scam and college is
people are going into debt they're
paying a lot of money but I want to ask
you a question you said it's a scam for
some people who is it a scam for yeah
for people who specifically aren't ever
going to use it never use any of the
knowledge that they from it well you say
52% I don't think you can grant qualify
52% of people don't do that for example
for example my job that's not going to
be recommended like as like an economics
degree and most economics Majors AR
going to go into Tik Tok debating online
but I use the information that I learned
in college in like on in my job on a
daily basis so I still
qualities that are then used in my job
later on what percentage of kids that go
to college are being scammed can you I
don't think I don't think anyone knows
that it's dependent upon an individual I
have no clue shouldn't we try to find
out well if you'd like to find some
empirics on that I'd love to see it I I
just did so 41 41 well well the
Department of Education is a source no
the Department of Education doesn't say
41% of people it was a scam for or that
they didn't use any of the information
they learned in college you are you are
using so are you saying none of them use
any of the information can I say three
words without you interrupting me do any
of them use the information L on can I
say five words that interrupt you've
interruped me multip time multiple times
so since you say college is a scam for
some people it's a ballpark for the kids
that do not graduate 41% that ended up
going and not graduating were they
scammed uh no just because you go and
pay for a particular thing but then you
don't follow through with it doesn't
mean you were scammed maybe they were
you decided to pay for it oh you could
say some people are misled some people
are sing to these things some people are
met in are misled in the church and you
never answered my question on that
because you're trying to I did take that
time down so you don't have to answer
the question about Christianity because
you know your world if you looks
terrible well what about Christianity
you want me to answer we're talking I
think it's false because I was saying is
is church a scam if church is a scam
that'd be predicated off of the idea
that you're deceived into believing that
there's everlasting life specifically
from Christianity again so Christianity
has to be true so can you grant that
what's the argument Christianity is true
did the resur what the argument you're
going to let me finish three words in a
row appreciate it okay did the
resurrection happen uh I don't think the
resurrection occurred okay I disagree
okay so let me ask you a question a
perfect Creator is it possible for them
to not desire something imperfect a
perfect is a perfect Creator I'm sorry
what there's a perfect creator that
desires everything that's just perfect
how can they desire something imperfect
flaud well because maybe they want to
get to know themselves maybe they want
to see their own creation maybe they
love want get to know them can I can I
finish can I finish talking here okay
maybe because God loved the world so
much that his creation which rebelled
against him given agency and Free Will
rebelled against them then got eternal
life what we actually deserve and then
sent his son on a rescue mission to save
us from that the church is the bride of
Christ will save us from Damnation that
we deserve college is far from the Bride
Of America it's currently scamming the
Youth of this country and sending them
into Oblivion didn't answer the question
I I did no you didn't say how they could
desire something imperfect how how well
God can anything that later God can do
anything so even something logically
contradictory it's not logically
contradictory so desire something imp an
un can an Unstoppable can an Unstoppable
object can an Unstoppable object hit
aable
Force hey before we go any further we
want to take a moment to say thanks so
much to straight arrow news for powering
the fact checks in this video straight
arrow news is an app and website that is
on a mission to raise the bar on
journalism in a time of media bias and
mistrust their team of journalists
believe that unbiased news should be the
standard and not just the exception so
they report down the- Middle with facts
delivering news without bias filter or
spin plus their media Miss tool allows
you to discover news that's being
underreported or not even reported at
all by different sides of mainstream
media that's why we're so happy to be
partnering with straight arrow news the
work they're doing gives us a complete
picture of the news straight from our
phones and tablets with their app go to
san.com slss surrounded or click the
link in the description to check it out
by clicking that link you're not just
supporting this channel you're also
supporting a group of journalists that
are raising the bar on news and focusing
on serving you unbiased straight facts
thanks again to straight arrow news for
partnering with us on this episode now
let's get into it yeah my next claim is
that trans women are not
[Music]
women okay what's your name Sam nice to
meet you uh let's define our term
uh a woman is an adult female of XX
chromosomes you tell me what is a woman
I think a woman is somebody who
identifies as a woman got it so that's
not a definition that's like saying a
table is something that identifies as a
table give me an objective definition of
no it's not a table is an object well
tell tell a table can't identify as
anything it doesn't haveo you have to
give me an objective definition of what
a woman is if I decided right now that I
wanted to identify as a woman I would be
a
woman okay but that's not that doesn't
answer the question I know but right now
I'm a man right so if that happened
right now woman once once a person makes
the decision to identify as a woman
woman that's a separate issue what is a
woman that's the definition no I know
but you have to tell me what a person
who identifies thems as a woman but you
have ident how do you know that they are
that thing how do I I don't need to know
what they I can ask them if I want to
know but there needs to be you need to
tell me what that thing is though
somebody who we're not getting anywhere
we're not getting any it's important
because it's like saying a giraffe is a
thing that looks like a giraffe or a
coyot thing that looks like a coyote
it's called circular reasoning you have
to give me a actual definition I don't
have to I I did give you a definition no
you said that a woman is something that
thinks they're a woman that doesn't give
me a definition that simply what would
you consider a definition then an adult
female with XX no no I mean like what
what makes that a
definition hello hi Juliana jul
um I don't necessarily think that you
can define a woman just by her
chromosomes women are so much more than
that they come in a variety of shapes
sizes colors and I don't necessarily
think that you can count out somebody
who's trans just because they don't have
a certain set of chromosomes there are
also people who are born I'm trying to
I'm drawing a blank uh intersects so XX
y or Y YX or just yeah or like x0
nothing so so natural mutations upon the
binary essentially right yes so but but
they don't have both sex organs that
both that both operate right yeah but
that also I don't think necessarily
works right because if it's X there's a
so you're either more male or more
female right so you might have both a
penis and vagina but there's never been
a case of someone who can impregnate
themselves okay I also don't necessarily
think that uh works for this situation
but um I also want to say that one of my
best friends is trans and I would say
that she's more of a woman than I am I
think that women Define themselves by
multiple things not just their sex
organs if somebody asked me who I was as
a woman I would not say I have a vagina
totally fair no I think you said
something smart so you said that person
is more of a woman than you are
therefore you're greatting off a
definition of something accomplishes
Womanhood what is that I think it's well
that's the thing too and I I do think
that gets a little complicated right
because there are social norms for a
gender but I do think we try to break
that right for sure but you said that
specific friend is more of a woman than
you are
why I think she's a better person than
me I think she Liv women are better
people she's a better woman than I am
I'm not saying women are better people
no but what what makes a woman a woman
because you said she's more of a woman
than you are so I want to know what that
definition is right okay I'm going to
let somebody else go thank
you okay all right Parker what is a
woman uh a woman is an adult human
person that has a desire to be in
accordance with a particular set of
Social and cultural norms that are
typically associated with a female sex
Define a man associate you're looking at
one XY chromosomes and okay do does God
the father have XY chromosomes
Incarnation we literally have a
religious a father and he's he him but
he's not a man we have a religious so a
man is someone with XY chromosomes but
he doesn't have XY chromosomes he's
still a man he still use prefer actually
very interesting in the original Hebrew
Adonai do you know what Adon is it's the
Hebrew word for God it's actually
genderless but in this in actually in
the scriptures they use he right and
they use the masculine Jesus Christ came
to Earth as a man not as a woman not as
gender queer but let's go back to
but God the father is a man right All
fathers are men well first of all
there's a trinity so God the father is
neither man nor woman he is omnicient
omnipotent he is all being on top of so
why do you use he well I did not the
scriptures do you could use woman you
could say her you could use him but the
way that the language is structured
again it is so the God the father is so
above gender it is so above any of our
understanding with glory and
understanding again because you have to
make a choice either he or him him or
her in the Original Scriptures let's go
back to I'm Happ father AR so I'm I'm so
some fathers are not men and boys not
men or boys I'm sorry some fathers are
not male no of course they are I'm not
wait so God the father is a male hold on
God the father so where where do we get
God the father from what what Greek word
from your scripture well from ABA right
which is a very close personal ter
you're not answering my questions and
you bring up random language that
doesn't matter well it actually does no
it doesn't but let me let me get down to
the root of it because I CU he's not a
man you know he's not a man under your
worldview yet you still use his
preferred pron you still call him a man
you don't do that with trans people
because you're transphobic that's why
okay got it but Christ is a man I'm
happy to get into the sexuality and
gation not of the Trinity okay before
Incarnation there's no penis there's no
XY chromisms there's no small G second
let's think about it if that's correct
how is it then Jacob saw the face of God
okay so if there's hold on if there was
not before the Incarnation how did Jacob
see the face of God how did Jacob
wrestle with God characters can have
faces without biology how did Jacob
wrestle with God so so okay do you think
that he has a body well or was that a
figurative notion of of wrestle that's
that's a mystery of the scriptures I'm
not here well it is I'm not here to
debate theology can we go back to we
talking about he does he actual biology
you keep trying to Pivot because you
know this debunks you what what biology
does your God have what what well the
one of Christ Our Lord the I meant
before Incarnation well I I to be honest
I don't quite know and I don't think the
scriptures are you don't know what a man
is well you can't Define what a man is
it's a little opaque again you're
looking at a man but your your video the
largest video on Tik Tok is what is a
woman 20 million views but you don't
know what a man is on your own world VI
I said you're looking at a man right
wait but God the father doesn't meet
that criteria am I looking at a man okay
good just make a man that's de beating
you in
that's fine so let me ask you a question
though so do you think that anybody can
become a woman um I think that anyone
who meets my criteria is a woman what's
your criteria again adult human person
that has a desire to be in accordance
with a particular set of Social and
cultural norms that are typically
associated with the female sex can
Society ever be wrong sure but like it's
it's it's a it's a desire to be in
accordance with a set of Social and
cultural norms can I become if I black
face no because it's not a desire that
you have to be in accordance with
particular because race is defined
phenotypically based upon the expression
to other people but you're by some
standard you're judging that do you
think there's a phenotypical expression
of someone who's white and someone who's
black like I see you're white because
you're phenotypical expression right so
but do you think but Rachel doelle that
said she is black and culturally black
is she black does she does she have
phenotypically uh characteristics we
would associate phenotypical I'm not
sure what that word means photp it's
going to be the like the the
expression yes okay so she she she could
pass as a black person wait so she
doesn't have the melanin content she's
borderline no okay so then she's not
black okay so you're able to say who is
black and not black that's how we Define
it in society no okay got it so but
is there an objective definition of who
is Black wait language is all subjective
Linguistics professionals indicate it's
subjective language is all subjective
yes absolutely every word you just used
was created by other human beings that
are engaging in conversation you might
think it's created by God but even then
it's still subjective now wewh God
subject now we're getting similar is the
word and the value behind murder
objective or subjective well I think
morality is subjective but you think
it's subjective too because it comes
from God that's interesting wait does it
come from God or independent of God well
no it's of course it comes from God it's
Transcendent being that's subjective yes
it is if it comes from God it's it's
specifically subjective it comes
independent of God then it's objective
what you just told me is is also comp
moral antirealism so let's go back to
the Ten Commandments you don't
understand meta ethics well I I hold on
a second what does subjective morality
mean what does subjective morality means
that it it comes in everybody's own
opinion their own form not dependent on
a stance God is a stance and that's the
truth of morality so if let's let's
let's believe do you believe in the if
everybody believed in the concept of God
the Transcendent God that there was a
Ten Commandments and we should live by
them right is that objective morality no
just because people agree do make it
objective again independent of stance AG
is what is objective morality
that sorry thanks we we'll be back at it
next
time Mason get are you nice to meet you
okay so I think it's a little scummy
that you're plagiarizing the whole Matt
Walsh thing like your thing is the
worship of Israel like that I pay him
royalties okay for sure well do you want
to talk about sex first or do you want
to talk about gender I don't think
gender exists I think it's a it's a it's
a term that John money and Judith Butler
created over the last 40 years that
basically is a filler for personalities
okay well if we're talking about sex
which it seems like you're saying is the
exact same thing um would you say sex is
binary by definition for sure yes
absolutely okay so you're already in
correct like sex is not binary it's
bodal so if you look at a distribution
graph we're going to see people in two
camps majority of the time but there are
going to be externalities on both ends
of the spectrum and in the middle we
talk about inter however with intersects
though they are mutations of a binary
correct no we're we're talking about on
but which we're talking about an entire
Spectrum which which by definition
defeating your expression of what a
binary is by saying that there are
externalities but but let me ask you a
question that like
xxy you're trying to create this own box
and then use any examples that are
outside of that box you brought up
justify that box again you brought up
interex we're talking about reality you
brought up intersex what sex organs
which one is more dominant what do you
mean in an xxy situation can you explain
your your point of view obviously you
have more female characteristics than
male characteristics in an xxy or it
might be y YX one of the one of the two
the point is that you do you do not have
both we could see people with female
reproductive organs that have XY and we
can see the vice versa people with male
reproductive organs that have ex sex so
I think you said something about gender
though I think that's more inter to get
into do you understand how the convers
we moving off of sex CU you're seing
that argument no I'm not seing it you
want to keep going into it we can if
You' like okay so so besides male and
female what categories exist we we have
people that are interex we have people
that are on the other ends of the bodal
distribution gra are you are you aware
what bodal means versus binary um
somewhat of an understanding okay well
you can be presented with a graph after
this by the people that you brought with
you but it's it's actually B
distribution just like constantly going
to condescending type talk is not going
to be fruit I'm just trying to match
your energy with the people that you
treated that were trying to have a
trans women are not women do you agree
with that uh I would say that trans
women are women because people that
exist under the category of women people
that exist under the category of men are
still humans so that category how how is
that defined well I wouldn't limit it to
things like genitals or things like
chromosomes which seems like you want to
do um what type of genitals would you
say I have since there OB genitals I'm
not obsess genitals but I could do a
blood sampling right now and I could see
exactly what you are because every
single one of your trillions of cells
are either coded with XX or XY no no how
much surgery or whatever I think that
you are man but you could fool me you
could take hormones you could play
camouflage like I could fool you to be
Hispanic if I had the right Hollywood
makeup director that doesn't mean that
you are the thing though but but you're
going from an objective biological
perspective which we've already talked
about with sex I'm talking about a
social construct or a social utility so
like if we were at a restaurant right
I'm sitting down and I'm sitting down at
the table and you're telling the waiter
hey I want to go sit with blank what
would you use with you he doesn't know
my name yeah I'm sitting over there that
guy yeah yes correct guy you're going to
typically use he or him or you're going
to say that guy like you just said
correct because you're ascribing the
male gender to me based on my I say I
could be an error maybe you are a
biological woman and then you'd correct
yourself right that take may maybe maybe
not so that's what we that is exactly
what we're trying to say we're so the
question is that do you think that
Womanhood can then be assumed just
through costume design it's not costume
design what is it then it's performative
social characteris so you could act
that's what gender is great it so you
could it's like a theater troop it's not
a theater troop these are social these
are social can be appropriated no
they're C they're categories that's what
it is so so there's nothing inherent
about the chromosomes there's nothing
that correct wow we disagree so there's
nothing inherent about having a period
or being able to give birth or the
specific hormonal makeup in different
cultures we've ascribed that to
Womanhood if you go back to other
cultures spending thousands of years
you'll see a difference when it like for
example the Mayans had plenty of people
that were schizophrenic right so that
means nothing to me right okay we have
people that say they're hearing things
from God would you say that
schizophrenic well not necessarily it
built western civilization and common
law and due process and individual
rights defense of The Unborn and the
greatest civilization ever you know that
voice from God happened to build the
greatest nation ever to exist in the
history of the world that's fine okay I
think the minds would say the same thing
that's the problem with presuppositional
arguments is that you could say mean
God's telling me right
now do you think that's real can we go
visit the M Nation they didn't last that
long did they yeah overkilling and
violence and you can justify that if you
like you mean all the child sacrifice
this is the kind of that why I'm trying
to match it is because you mean all the
child sacrifice the mines and incin dead
on the top of temples great civilization
you want to go back in the Old Testament
let's bring Parker up in here talk about
all the the child child marriage we can
talk about the justification of R where
was child sacrifice ever in the Bible um
when Isaac or Isaac was almost
sacrificed by his dad he wasn't though
because at the beginning of Genesis so
God just said like no just kidding dog
don't actually why because at the
beginning of Genesis 16 said I'm going
to test to Pro obedience yeah that's
right so now you know it so actually no
there was no child sacrifice in the
Bible it was a Prohibition on child
sacrifice the but anyway that's a little
bit of a rabbit hole do you understand
at least can you sympathize with our
perspective okay that that I'll calm it
down a little bit I apologize for the
con I mean you're doing it's it's fine
but you see where this could get wildly
out of control at least on the I don't
see how it get out of control because
even in sports for example you think
that there's no there's so this is this
is something that we might be able to
agree upon right Sports were not
archaeologically dug up right the rules
of sports they are things that we've
created as a society we have decided as
a society the most Fair categorization
is male Sports and female sports now as
we've been able to understand or at
least bring into the Forefront people
who don't identify with the bind we
still have to allow all people that are
women in the women's category and all
men that are men in the women's category
that includes CIS and trans if you'd
like to change that category because you
think it's unfair we can do that that's
what's awesome about arbitrary rules is
we can decide hormones I might not know
this but like when the Greeks started
the Olympics 2,000 years ago did they
have like a bunch of dudes wrestling
with women I don't even think they
allowed women to compete well I might be
wrong on that but that kind of proves
the point though that there was a what
did we do to allow women we changed the
rules right no but that by definition
therefore there is something from body
composition bone mass long density
testosterone and estrogen rates so
Endocrinology is different if you if
you'd say the majority of males in the
botal distribution graph we're going
back to that you can say hey we we want
this level of hormones in this
particular category and we can separate
it by hormones I agree with you that a
majority of men are majority of sity you
got to be like 99.9% I don't know Ronda
Rousey could kick my ass I will say that
no for sure but I mean but could she
kick Conor McGregor's ass well now we're
talking about the Peaks right she said
theend no because you're talking about
the peaks of two different categories in
the same sort of right because because
why she's a CIS woman well she's a CIS
woman and a CIS man but yes and he could
kick her tail right yes I would agree
okay for sure right because CIS men and
CIS women have different hormone levels
if you want to change the hormones we
can change the categorization you're
saying that you want men and women Bar
None and you say that's the most like
Fair category then we have to
all men but again there those things
don't so I just want to be clear so
because I think I'm tracking your
argument is that in the University of
Pennsylvania swim team when Thomas swam
against biological women that was you're
perfectly fine with that I think as long
as we have the categories that way
thanks good to meet you
yeah you want to get him in this isn't
debated yet no no no you're fine you're
fine you're fine what's your name hi my
name is pry nice to meet youney nice to
meet you go ahead pry pry t r you're
totally yeah um okay so I kind of want
to go back to a little earlier you said
that a Parker has lower T than you so
would you say a joke yeah no no I'm I'm
fully I'm fully aware of a joke but I
guess like on that on that point do you
think that like tea has to do or
testosterone has to do with your manhood
like well yes and no I mean for if you
are looking at typical testosterone
estone rates of women they are far
different than those of men but for
example like your testosterone rate goes
down when you have children for example
when you're a man that doesn't make you
less of a man they go they go down by by
400 points okay but like when we were
talking earlier about like sports right
and you were saying that the reason why
it's unfair for like like for example a
trans woman who used to be a man to be
like competing in women's sports you
said you cited that they have higher
testosterone levels one of about 50
characteristics also lung density the
men's hearts are bigger we have greater
bone B bone bone density muscle mass
okay be faster T to be stronger I I
understand but like those factors all
come from the hormones during the
development process say correct no not
necessarily no I mean most of them do
well not all of them so for example you
could try to pump a young girl's body
with testosterone at 8 years old and you
can get them stronger you cannot
necessarily get them on par with a
biological male at puberty you cannot
you could try okay but like because
there's something in the coding of our
genetics the coding of our genetics
which is often like controlled by like
different like I guess parts of our DNA
and also the hormones that are produced
that affect the the effective coding
ology it's a big part because for
example if you just give a kid
testosterone that doesn't even get them
close to becoming a male or estrogen
giving them a female they might get
characteristics that are close to that
right okay but it does for but I mean
like there's no perfect image of like
this is what a female looks like this is
what a male looks like like we all get
our periods at different ages some of us
like like and also like for example like
there are many circumstances where
Womanhood is just not one thing right
it's a multitude of experiences every
single person can you define what
Womanhood is that's an interesting
question for you well no I can't Define
what Womanhood is and the reason why is
because it's something that's an
individual experience for every single
person right like my experiences what I
have experienced throughout my life is
not going to be the same as another
woman who may have like grown up in a
different environment disagreement but
not Clarity I say that being a woman or
Womanhood is an objective thing right
but objective outside of one own's
opinions or experien so but are we at
the point where we're discussing where
this is like not something based on your
chromosones but something maybe based on
a construct well no it also can be
objectively witnessed in empirical ways
in biological ways in scientific ways
okay so to clarify we're still
discussing whether Womanhood is on
chromosomes or not if if you'd like to
discuss that it's deeper than just
chromosones right right I'm just trying
to for ex for example if we look at spec
scans or brain scans of men and women
98% of the time artificial intelligence
can tell you which one is the men and
which one is the male female okay so our
different parts of our brains fire so
for for men for men for example are
amygdalas are not as highw working as
women you know what amydala is the
threat assessment part of your so
obviously like your birth so there's a
difference between the concept or what
sex is which is a biological aspect and
what gender is which is a social
construct I reject gender completely as
a different word it's really personal
that's where the debate is it's the
existence of gender gender gender means
personality okay I don't doubt that
biological men might havein how would
you define race on that point how would
I Define how you def race well race is a
very difficult topic top okay because I
think that it's a really important thing
to discuss when it comes if I draw if I
draw blood is it ethnic lines is it if
you have a blood sample of a black
individual and a white individual I
can't tell you which one is which if I
have a blood sample of a man and a woman
I can tell you which one is which just
by running very simple Elementary blood
tests so for example if there was a
Hispanic or a white there is no
difference in the genetic coding there
just isn't why is it important that
someone's oh okay
my next claim is that kamla Harris is a
Dei
[Music]
candidate a lot of competition Mason
yeah exactly good to see you good to see
you again um can I define what a Dei
candidate is I I think that you're GNA
say because she's black and she's a
woman she's appointed because Joe Biden
promised that and it's is not a
testament to her not only that but also
in the her getting the nomination of the
Democrat Party they said repeatedly we
do not want to pass over a black female
okay so just those two things but the
first one is stronger you're right Joe
Biden said I'm going to put on my vice
presidency a black female right right so
his criteria yeah and that was like
Karen bass and KLA Harris so she was not
chosen because of her intellect or her
accomplishments or because of any of
that it was because she happened to fit
a couple boxes in fact Amy kachar the
vetting at the time was that Amy kobar
would have been a better VP and kamla
ended up getting it so it's just a
statement of fact that she is there not
because of her Brilliance or
accomplishments but because of her
ethnicity so KLA Harris first and
foremost there are a lot of criticism
that you can give to her on why she
wouldn't be an effective president it
shouldn't be because she's a woman or
because she's black and it seems to be
that you're I'm just I just want people
to understand and agree she didn't earn
this she she absolutely did she has she
has a career where she's been not only a
de de stands one earn it just so we're
clear but like it stands for diversity
Equity inclusion I like the meme though
I I know what it is but do you at least
admit and acknowledge that when Joe
Biden was searching for a VP he cared
more about skin color and a female than
the smartest best person so the the
whole conversation with this affirmative
action with Dei the whole reason why
people bring it in is to make this
imaginary scenario that there's a super
qualified white man who was overpassed
by this unqualified stupid idiot person
of color which is such a terrible
analogy because it's not true absolutely
not true that's not what it is Jo bid
did not say I'm going to choose an
unqualified person just his own team
he's saying that I'm going to have two
qualified people if one comes from a
different experience it might be better
to have a diversity and have a better
perception in forms of he said at the
South Carolina debate that will pick a
black woman as my vice president
secondly Amy kachar came out is this a
random black woman that he plucked off
the street or is this a qualified DEA
general attorney who's had a decorated
career leading government positions you
can but you keep rambling about things
that just aren't relevant to what we're
talking it is relevant AB kachar in
vetting came across as the more
qualified candidate why because they
said kamla Harris wasn't very smart
wasn't very bright that's their own
vetting documents from the from who Joe
Biden's own vetting documents show why
would he go against that because the
base of the Democrat Party demands
tribal politics and Dei politics over
competency that's completely inur he
stated to Jim kber said I will only
endorse you in the South Carolina
primary if you say that you're going to
put a black person preferably a black
female on your ticket with you therefore
you winnow the entire universe down and
say I'm only going to choose from this
criteria and let's just think more
broadly if you're about to have heart
surgery would you rather have a heart
surgeon that's good and excellent knows
what he's doing or someone that is a
black female so and being president is
more important than being a heart
surgeon aren't you on record saying that
you'd be terrified if there was a black
pilot that was was flying I did say that
but what why what was the full quote I I
personally I don't know if you want to
expand on yeah so this this ties into
this United Airlines said that half of
all their new hes are going to be black
or women and that standards and pursuit
of Excellence is not going to be taken
as um seriously as diversity when I'm
flying a plane I want to know my pilot
is there because they're a good pilot
not because they fit some Dei box damn
it I wish we could have a better
conversation I'm sorry man
fast man okay so let's say that KLA
Harris was the Dei hire as vice
president do you think she's also a deer
as the Presidential nominee for the
Democratic party potentially yeah I mean
they decided to go to her almost
immediately because she is the VP but
also because she fits some criteria
boxes but let me ask you you you don't
think it's because Joe Biden nominated
or no for sure that's part of it of
course it is but let me ask you what's
her greatest achievement accomplishment
I'd say her greatest achievement or
accomplishment is completely destroying
their Republican party within like 2
weeks of being nominated like in the
polls she's just absolutely
huh
sorry how are you nice to see you what's
your name Amanda Amanda so you believe
because kamla is black and a woman she
was chosen for belief her own team Joe
Biden said that he said I said that yeah
he said I'm first because beforehand he
said I'm going to choose a black female
for vice president president he didn't
say I'm going to choose the most gifted
or the most talented or the most
accomplished he said so he said I'm
going to choose a black female and so by
definition that is Dei that is not the
definition of Dei by him saying that he
was going to choose a black female that
could insinuate that he already had
comma mind for the role no way does that
insinuate that she's Dei what is Dei
then Dei would be choosing somebody
based on their race no it's giving
people of color the opportunity to be
welcomed into spaces in which they
typically AR able to get there's never
been a female black vice president and
why do you think that is well not why
you just said that's
Dei so by definition she's Dei okay so
she represents diversity within the
government no I'm saying she got
elevated because she was a black female
because if that were the case I'd be the
president right now do do you do you
think do you think kamla Harris was
chosen because of her intelligence her
qualifications and her intelligence
really wow if you compare what's
greatest accom what's her greatest
accomplish prosecutor within the
Northern California area you mean
letting out violent criminals and
turning San Francisco one of the most
murderous dangerous arson fied homeless
field slums in the country that's her
greatest accomplishment see I actually
went to UC Berkeley so I lived there I
don't know if you did uh I went around
Berkeley is a slum Berkeley is a slum
have you stepped into Berkeley yes I
have you think Oakland and Berkeley have
you lived in Berkeley I've lived in
Oakland as well your basing your you
think the Bay Area is like a good area
in this country I'm from Vegas so I'm
not from the bay born raised in Vegas
and went to UC Berkeley CH graduated
this year what you're saying literally
in no way shape formar so you think her
overseeing San Francisco becoming the
laughing stock of the country is fris is
not the laughing stock of the country if
anything that'ss Florida no offense but
hold on if that's the case why are
millions of people moving to Florida and
millions of people leaving California
because there are cheaper rates there
people are moving to Las Vegas Las Vegas
it's cheaper because it's a better run
State and we don't give money to
is Northern California is not the
entirety of California there's Southern
California Cali why is it that so many
businesses are leaving San Francisco if
she did such a great job lowering crime
do you know businesses go where things
are cheapest to operate why are they
cheaper because they're better run
states do you realize that California is
one of the most populated states within
the US so obviously cost are going to be
high not only that but land within this
state is also very very very minimal so
hold on you have you have tons of land
you're one of the biggest states in
country yes it is one of the biggest
lands but do you also take into account
the population that's here yes Florida
and Texas have a greater combined
population than California and Cal
California has more population and more
more land mass than Florida why is it
that San Francisco has a declining
population and Miami Tampa Orlando have
an increasing population what does this
have to do with Dei because she ran San
Francisco poorly and she was chosen as a
VP because she was a black woman San
Francisco she was the da da of San
Francisco she's Prosecuting and then she
became the AG of California where crime
went up homelessness went up arson went
up kidnapping went up is it not the job
of the police to get the criminal the
attorney the attorney general of the
state is the top cop of the state yes
and what did she do to lower crime in
California she convicted those who were
guilty why did crime go up because as
the population increases and this econ e
economy gets worse no
wor people are becoming more and more
desperate which leads to C of crime
thank
[Applause]
you mine will be quick mine will be
really quick goad okay so real quick
you're saying that the only reason she
was elected was is because she's black
so that trumps her being a district
attorney and all the this is not my
words I'm just going on Joe Biden's own
words Joe Biden said I'm going to preset
criteria based based on black women and
therefore she met that met that criteria
and that's why she was selected no why I
think he was what he was trying to say
is oh I'm she's just black she was just
calling her black she's not saying I'm
doing he's not saying he's not saying
I'm doing this because she's black
that's not what she said he made a
public promise before the selection even
began and the process began I will put a
black woman on the ticket so you're
saying her being dist attorney doesn't
matter that's not why but an aw being a
failed
businessman and making all the comments
weird comments he's made well hold on a
second that doesn't have like what I'm
getting at though is that if she was not
a black woman she never would have been
chosen as vice president her record was
abysmal she was a terrible Attorney
General of California she had
poorly I'm so sorry I'll be quior I'll
be quick I'm so sorry she she gets the
next one yeah all right sorry yeah I
just have to know do you think Tim Waltz
is a Dei candidate okay I just wanted to
see consist Dei does not mean black
timal was only chosen because the
Democrat Party is doing so poorly with
white men that they tried to find a
white man that they could put on the
ticket but then also true Tim Walls is
the first White Dei candidate in history
okay in the Democratic primaries KLA
harros was performing incredibly well
and she wasn't performing well in the
primaries just because she was black she
was performing well in the primaries
because during her time as a senator she
spoke incredibly eloquently I used to
watch hold on a second how did she do in
the Democrat primaries she did like much
better than Amy kachar she didn't even
make it to Iowa she dropped out months
ahead of the first primary she was super
unpopular not well-liked her campaign
fizzled out so she was she was popular
initially initially yes and then the
more people learned about her the more
realized she was awful well it was
mostly because like progressives are
really upset about her being a DA which
like can be like that that's a
completely different why aren't
progressives upset about that now I mean
they are but oh they are that's new to
me everyone's talking about how great
prosecut she is progressives are
definitely upset about the like how um
like the Biden Administration has
handled like the atrocities and gods and
how like they they are definitely things
that Democrats are upset about however
that's not the point of this
conversation i that's correct that is
not Point that's not the point what the
point is is that a lot
of a thanks
guys okay hi how are you doing right so
um you keep saying that K Harris is a
dii candidate and I feel my main fallacy
with this argument is that competency
can't be
objectively determined because we all
have subjective definitions of what a
competent politician is but my question
for you is if kamla Harris is a Dei
candidate why is she beating Trump in
the polls right now we'll see what
happens in November okay but she's
currently beating Trump in the polls so
either if the polls are right I grant
you that she's incompetent or or maybe
she's a new candidate with a big surge I
I I would caution you being a little
like this point in the election getting
too cocky because we remember what
happened with I'm not getting cocky I'm
asking you to answer a question if she
is incompetent how could she beat the
president who you said is an as of the
timing of this filming can you name to
me how many times she sat down for an
interview what no she refuses to talk to
the Press refuses to take questions
she's not one sit down interview in
nearly 25 days at the filming of this
interview mind you which I don't know a
very weird point to make why would I
count how many times kamla Harris has
interview because she refuses to take
questions from the press and media like
shouldn't you do that if you're the city
vice president
she's uh he actually did three last
Sunday and one today with Meet the Press
so the quality the qualification of a
good president is to take an interview
if you can't take a single question but
let me ask you this because it's on you
can what's her greatest accomplishment
as vice president as vice president
being the first female all black
president we've never had no no like I
got that but like what what's her
accomplishment that made people's lives
better I don't know vice presidents
don't really do much to be honest can
you name one thing she's done that's
good no probably
not thank you the inflation reduction
act really did that lower
inflation what's your name Brad Brad
Brady nice to meet you uh I like the
idea 30 seconds on 30 seconds off I
think the best thing I could say about
this is you have your opinion and I can
have mine you believe that Donald Trump
was a good president I maybe don't
believe that you believe that KLA Harris
is a Dei candidate for the position of
President I don't believe that what I'm
getting to is what do you gain from this
if I concede and say that KLA Harris is
a Dei candidate what do you gain because
I know what it is you're baiting us into
rage so that you can make money on your
Tik Tok account you're baiting college
students all over the world and to
arguing with you over these fallacies
you throw a red herring out there and
you're making money from this account
well we're sitting here and looking
stupid first of all I don't control this
account I'm guest here this is Jubilee
media and they're going to edit it how
they see fit okay number one number two
it needs to be acknowledged that she
didn't earn it she didn't win a Democrat
primary she dropped out in the Democrat
Primary in 2020 she's never been likable
she's got there simply because of race
not because of Competency not because
she's good at her job and I think that's
wrong and it needs to be called out
you're bringing up qualitative examples
these are all subjective qualitative
examples her race her competency her
dropping out of the election these
that's not what you said earlier this is
I'm talking about the points you've just
bought up multiple qualitative points
and these points can be believed by you
and not by me as you believe in a God
and I don't these are qualitative
arguments that you're making against me
for this and I can believe differently
than you and I think we can agree to
disagree on this one okay fine perfect
okay I think this is going to take the
entire time you're welcome 30 on 30 off
how do you feel about the Senate
uh far as her her tiebreaking vote of
the Senate no no no I'm just saying like
Senate like like the Senate is
technically Dei in a certain sense for
like small states like Wyoming gets
people W Wyoming get a greater vot than
in California like Rhode island in
Hawaii I'm giving you an example
California I get less of a vote than
someone who exists in Wyoming so we're
giving people in Wyoming more say than
they necessarily should given that
they're one individual so why do you
believe in Dei as it relates to how our
government is set up we don't believe in
Dei in terms of allowing for people who
are black or who are women to be in
positions of power that they have not
been allowed in historically speaking so
um is the electoral college and the
Senate based on race it's it's
predicated off of diversity equity and
inclusion right like inclusion of of of
country areas inclusion of rural areas
inclusion of white men like you okay so
you mean like Hawaii I'm referencing I'm
referencing you could say smaller States
or places that have less people in it
obviously would be able to have more of
a say per individual so your argument is
that US Senate is a Dei I I can be
honest I've never heard that argument
but I think it's a little silly but how
is it silly argue against it instead of
just saying it's silly well right so
it's silly on its face because first of
all we have on the House Representatives
is proportional to
population but but the Senate isn't so
it's de it's not Dei yes it is what why
would you say it's diversity Equity
inclusions because Wyoming gets two
senators they're their own sovereign
state aren they for Country areas for
rural areas equity for rural areas for
smaller States so let's go back to the
Federal papers and the founding fathers
why was the Senate compos tell me why
it's not de like under your definition
why not based on race and by way it does
have to be based it's not based on
equity and it's not based on inclusion
can you have based upon different
character other than race whether or not
you're a woman whether or not let let me
finish why it's because we are a
collection of States we are not a
federal project so states rights usurp
federals do you know what the 17th
amendment is do you know do you know the
why the Articles of Confederation failed
yes but what is the 10th Amendment
because had to right had too much power
that's why we specifically aded the let
me let me make one point okay which is
how did we us to elect
Senators it' be population no we used to
elect Senators based on state
legislatures so the Senate is an
extension of the state legislative
bodies that's not Dei that's federalism
that's the way that our system is set up
which is a bottom up citizen-led
government to allow the states which are
first and foremost Sovereign so it goes
in this lad in this country that's still
de for those States for those country
areas no because it's blind it's not
that
oh is not only based on race hold on a
second diversity for for Country
diversity for World equity for World an
inclusion of that's an inter point is
only because associate with Harris let
me ask you a question is there a single
instance in Corporate America or Dei is
implemented where diversity means
anything other than skin color diversity
so diversity view women women what fine
how about chromosone or diversity or
skin color so so so skin color there's
gender you had to you have to move the
goal poost a little bit because you got
destroyed there all right but there's
also no I'm just asking a very simple
question the answer is no because our
system of do mean that's not DEET your
Senate is Dei what was your definition
though what what is what was your
definition diversity Equity inclusion
diversity doesn't only apply to race
you're just saying other people definity
Equity inclusion to be based on race you
didn't though let me finish because
you're saying it didn't earn it you know
who did earn it South Dakota and North
Dakota when they charted themselves into
States Wyoming didn't earn it because
they have less into a state hold on
all right who really wants to go I I
don't want to pick on I don't want to
pick on somebody who doesn't want to get
picked on
okay
um you want to debate wa what is the top
whatever you want so you're you're the
affirmative I'm the
negative yeah let's do it you're good
with 10 minutes I don't want to put you
in a spot you don't want to be in no no
no let's do it let's fun you sure
[Applause]
okay okay I guess the claim I'm making
is that affirmative action is
constitutional tell me about your plan I
wanted to talk about affirmative action
because we haven't really gotten to it
and it's recently been revoked based on
the new Supreme Court ruling um and I
firmly believe that affirmative action
is constitutional and is a right that
certain American citizens deserve and I
just wanted to your thoughts on that um
well the 14th amendment allows for equal
protection regardless of race and it's a
colorblind Amendment and the whole idea
of affirmative action is to try to give
people
extra um boost based on their skin color
or their racial background which by
definition Cuts underneath the idea of
equal protection okay um so do you know
why the 14th amendment was founded and
the equal protection and Equal Rights
Act yeah the 14th amendment was a post
Civil War amendment 145 167 we all
during Reconstruction so what was it in
response to slavery oh and who were
slaves well that's that's an important
point so the do you think affirmative
action will help heal the
multigenerational problems of slavery I
do I really do because um so let's just
talk about the history for a second
slavery begins in the early 1800s
earlier no slavery 1816 is the beginning
of slavy
1619 oh yeah I guess it would be okay
first slaves come in 16 19 doesn't end
until 1800s 1880s then we go into Jim
Crow laws starting in
1877 and black people are not given
equal rights until officially 1965 would
you agree with that that's generally the
the correct telling yeah so you know
1960s 197 just so we're clear that black
Americans able to serve in office in the
early 1900s they were able to vote
throughout the 1900s but yes there were
pole taxes there was Jim Crow laws there
was was segregation of course there was
and we have to be yeah delal not to
acknowledge those things okay so we can
acknowledge all of those things can we
also acknowledge due to the laws under
Jim Crow that black people were
significantly hindered from economic
advancement this is a really important
question the data shows not really it
was evil it was terrible but black
Americans are poor today in 2024 than
they were in the 1950s yes why do you
think that is good question so we have
the Civil Rights Act we have more
benefits more government programs
something changed between the 1950s and
2024 so there's two answers to this
question either America got more racist
since 1950s 2024 so like that 70-year
period because blacks America black
Americans are worse off today per capita
they you agree with that okay good yeah
than in the 1950s or there's another
explanation and I think the truth is
somewhere in the middle which is I think
you would acknowledge that the The
Disappearance of the black father has
been the number one driver of black
poverty in this country now there are
reasons for that
yeah what do you think the reasons for
that are well culture is one would you
agree so actually let's go back to the
foundation prison pipeline all that
stuff but do at least can we at least
agree that black dad's not being around
is a bad thing anyone's father not being
around is a bad thing of course but 75%
of black youth are not raised with a
father in the home it's the highest of
any group in the country it used to be
25% in the 1950s so it's gone up
dramatically in 70 years okay so you are
blaming the fact that black people have
not be able been able to achieve
economic equality and advancement in
this country decre specifically and
solely because of the ABS not solely it
is the most primary ingredient reason
most so you think it's the absence of
black fathers correct and you think what
else public sector teer unions that have
kept these schools crummy and kids
aren't reading and teachers keep getting
paid we don't fire Bad Teachers that's a
big thing okay war on police in our
inner cities and not having enough
police and not actually put locking up
criminals let me hear me out for example
in Chicago do you know that only half of
all murders go go solved in the city of
Chicago that doesn't surprise me at all
that's a problem right that is a problem
yeah so we need more police more
detectives to solve those murders but I
I want to hear your points to I'm
talking too much so let's go back a
little bit to what you said in the issue
of policing now starting in the 1980s
and continuing onward there's been a War
on Drugs is this correct I like I like
the War on Drugs you like the War on
Drugs so during the War on Drugs it
created an epidemic of mass
incarceration specifically
if you're using drugs no or pedaling
drugs if you don't use drugs then you
don't go to jail right so you believe
that the criminal justice system is
Flawless no I've never said Flawless
there's a lot of people in jail that
shouldn't be in jail there's a lot of
problems in any system okay so wait
let's CL on that so you believe that a
lot of people who have gone to jail
shouldn't be in jail a small percent
what percent would you say 5% you would
say only 5% correct when you have a
system of justice you're going to have
scummy prosecutors you're going to have
bad defense attorneys I have a question
can I get a Google what percentage of
people currently incarcerated are black
it's way larger than well it's hold on
it's what it's way larger than no I know
but the fact the fact I'm saying the
fact I'm saying
5% so that's the point that I'm trying
to make exactly who am I Deb am I
debating here am I if your own
government is pumping drugs yeah so wait
okay so I want to make a quick you're
right black Americans are in prison far
greater than the percentage of the
population so the black Americans about
13 to 14% of the population about half
prisoners are black so blacks commit
more crimes than whites do they commit
more murders they commit more arson they
commit more kidnappings for example
blacks are 133% of the population and
they commit 58% of all the murders
that's not a War on Drugs That's a
culture problem okay so let's talk about
that culture black people have been
legislatively subjugated up until
1965 I'll give it I mean honestly it's
later but let's just say 1965 you do not
think that that 10 generations of
legislative subjugation and slavery
during that time
4,000 black men women and children are
lynched as the result of race riots in
this country you do not think that these
things have a lasting effect we have had
10 generations of subjugation and four
of legislative course they have an
impact but it's more on you to explain
why things got worse since the Civil
Rights Act more violent less fathers
around poorer why is that because of
mass incarceration and the unfair
criminalization of black men but let's
just take murders for example why are
why blacks are 13% of the population and
commit 58% of the murders why is that
because people in affluent and whiter
neighborhoods are not being policed at
the same are more I'm talking about dead
bodies there's no like we're not talking
about police saying we're talking about
murders why are so many blacks
committing murders outside of their
population okay let's take it back to
some history I'm curious for an answer
to that question going to give you one
so let's go to redlining okay red lining
red lining yes is why so many blacks are
killing each other no let me finish my
claim and then you can respond is that
okay okay so red lining federally
mandated or sustained by the FHA right
separating black Americans to
specifically impoverished and relegated
areas of the country we are incapable of
buying homes and putting Equity into
neighborhoods with lower crime rates and
better Educational Systems we do not
have access to things that would uplift
and help our community when you are put
in an
environment that
promotes and
reinforces social and economic
inequality you become desperate and are
forced to do things that maybe don't
align with your values what you're
making you're making an excuse for a lot
of murder when you have steal a high
concentration of a subjugated people in
one area if you were right when blacks
in America did not have the same rights
they had today there were less they were
less murderous there was less Breakin
why is that so I'm sorry are you trying
to say that blacks Thrive under
subjugation no I'm not I'm saying they
I'm asking you the question the data
shows they were actually better in the
1940s it was bad it was evil but what
happened something changed they
committed less crimes maybe they afraid
I mean
4,000 black men women and children were
killed in violent Lynch Mark that's your
explanation but I racial Terror
permeated American culture for hundreds
of years Black America is worse than it
has
been years the generational psych of an
entire group of people I'm sure it did
I'm not discounting that I'm just trying
to understand why is it the more social
welfare we've done so we've spent 20
trillion dollar on uplifting black
communities 20 trillion and black
Americans are poor we've done everything
that's been asked
you haven't done everything that's been
asked
though subsidized housing Medicaid
public schooling going subsidized
College we're talking about2 trillion
have been spent on the Great Society and
yet Black America is poorer more
murderous more dangerous so there's an
explanation I'm asking you we are not
asking for handouts we are asking for
equity and part of equity equity mean
you mean taking from other people excuse
me it means sharing which is something
that you guys seem to have a very hard
time doing sharing so somebody has to
explain why black America and you
haven't is 13% of the population and
commits 58% of the murders black people
have built and founded the
society thank
you I was very smart group very
opinionate there were a couple other
people I kind of felt bad for them they
had a lot of strong opinions but they
just weren't ready for Prime Time
overall very good group very impressive
Republicans tend to just focus on like
preventing you from arguing your point
not actually countering the points that
you come up with he often will switch
the topic like do a lot of Gish
Galloping and like kind of filibustering
to get people to not be able to make the
points that they want to make and I
definitely feel like he did that to me
look Charlie's a talented guy there's a
reason why he spoke at the RNC he's
media trained he's had conversations
like this before and he's built a career
on dunking on college students but for a
bunch of liberal students who don't have
that same type of media training and who
aren't as prepared to be in
confrontational formats like this I
thought they did a really good job of
our articulating their views yeah Mason
was the smartest kid for sure uh Parker
needs to calm down very smart but kept
on changing the topic uh but he's got
talent very annoying though smart but
Annoying Parker definitely gave Charlie
a run for his money yeah Parker ate
Parker ate that down one girl was very
nasty she was a very nasty person she
overly personalized it I honestly don't
regret any of the things I said the only
thing I would have taken back is I said
at the end I as I walked away I said I
hope your daughter can get away from you
that one was a dig and that was my bad
but honestly in the case of her being a
10-year-old pregnant and he won't let
her get medical help that's just wild to
me I can't believe that I think the
group did very great it's a very hard
environment for people to learn in these
types of areas but I think it's best
that people get involved in debate and
entertainment as it helps people grow
and critically think in our society I
thought it was very valuable I hope
people learned something um I think the
students were able to refine their
arguments and hopefully this gets seen
by millions of people where they're able
to see what side they land on uh but
yeah it's not easy just to stand there
be 20 on one but uh only at Jubilee
media